La-dee-la-lee-la-la la-lee-la
Hey!
Break away, break away 細|<さい胞|ぼうレ|<leベル|vel
break away break away sa i bo u level
挣脱吧 挣脱吧 每个细胞都是
Break away, break away at the cellular level
I don't need 不|<ふ本|<ほん意|い現|<げん状|じょう憂|<うれいてる
I don't need fu hon i gen jo u u re i te ru
我不需要 不情愿地哀叹现状
I don't need to grieve our current unwilling state
姿|<す#|が#|た仕|<し草|ぐ#|さ滑|<こ#|っ稽|け#|いでしょう？
su ga ta shi gu sa ko kke i de sho u
这副姿态模样 很可笑对吧？
That style and manner is ridiculous, right?
Don't you think? Don't you think?
难道你不觉得？
I'm so lazy 多|<た分|ぶ#|んそう
I'm so lazy ta bun so u
我懒到了家 大概就这样
I'm so lazy, that's probably the case
Fine sound 並|<な#|らべてるだけの人|<ひ#|と
fine sound na ra be te ru da ke no hi to
美妙音符 不过是他人的排列
Just someone arranging a fine sound
Trash, crash, toss away
丢弃 粉碎 通通扔掉
Don't you think? Don't you think?
难道你不觉得？
In this world この頭|<あ#|た#|まには
in this world ko no a ta ma ni wa
在这世上 在这脑海之中
In this world, in this head of mine
What a beautiful 舞|<まい散|<ちる花|<は#|なびら
what a beautiful ma i chi ru ha na bi ra
多么美丽 漫天飘舞的花瓣
What a beautiful petal that falls
バ|<баラ|лаラ|лаイ|йカ|ка 飲|<のみたいな
ba ra ra i ka no mi ta i na
巴拉莱卡酒 真想喝一杯
Balalaika I want to quench my thirst
La-dee-la-lee-la-la la-lee-la
Hey!
誰|<だ#|れもが大|<だ#|い体|たい C,R,A,Z,Y
da re mo ga da i ta i c r a z y
谁人都大抵 疯·狂·至·极
Generally speaking, everyone's C,R,A,Z,Y
Hey! Hey!
一|<い#|っ瞬|しゅ#|んの感|<かん情|じょうに
i sshun no kan jo u ni
任由那一瞬间的感情
So let this fleeting emotion
Ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
疾驰不停
Hey!
心|<こ#|こ#|ろは95 狂|<きょう気|きのサムライ
ko ko ro wa ninety five kyo u ki no sa mu ra i
心跳至九五 狂气的武士
My heart is beating 95, like a mad samurai
Hey! Hey!
血|<ち走|ば#|しらせた目|<めで引|<ひくくらい Ready to die
chi ba shi ra se ta me de hi ku ku ra i ready to die
以血红的眼引人侧目 随时赴死
I'm so ready to die that it's like it's attracting my bloodshot gaze
ハ|<heロー|llo陽|<ひは昇|<の#|ぼり
ha ro o hi wa no bo ri
哈喽 太阳升起
Say hello as the sun rises
あなたの空|<そ#|ら 真|<まっ黒|<く#|ろな空|<そ#|ら
a na ta no so ra ma kku ro na so ra
你的天空 漆黑如墨的天空
On your sky, that pitch black sky
荒|<あ#|ら々|あ#|らしく引|<ひきちぎって
a ra a ra shi ku hi ki chi gi tte
狂暴地将它撕裂
I'll rip it apart with my bare hands
ホラその場|<ば所|しょで
ho ra so no ba sho de
看啊 就在那个地方
You see, in that place
聞|<きこえてくる鼓|<こ動|ど#|うの仕|<し掛|かけ
ki ko e te ku ru ko do u no shi ka ke
传来心跳律动的机关
There's the trick of an audible heartbeat
轟|<と#|ど#|ろくのは己|<お#|の#|れの調|<し#|らべ
to do ro ku no wa o no re no shi ra be
轰鸣奏响的是自己的旋律
What roars out is my own tune
誰|<だ#|れかのじゃない 己|<お#|の#|れの調|<し#|らべ
da re ka no ja na i o no re no shi ra be
不属于任何人 是自己的旋律
My own tune - not someone else's
ラッダッダッ ラッダッダッ
ra dda dda' ra dda dda'
目|<めの前|<ま#|えに広|<ひ#|ろがる世|<せ界|か#|いはBlue
me no ma e ni hi ro ga ru se ka i wa blue
眼前无限展开的世界 一片蔚蓝
The world is blue, it stretches out before your eyes
ひとまず
hi to ma zu
总而言之
But for now
さぁ Move Move
sa a move move
来吧 行动起来
Let's move move
Speak about 生|<いき方|<か#|た There's no need
speak about i ki ka ta there's no need
谈论什么活法 毫无必要
There's no need to speak about our way of living
何|<な#|にをそんなに張|<はり切|<きって偉|<え#|らそうに
na ni o son na ni ha ri ki tte e ra so u ni
何必那样干劲十足 趾高气昂
What's got you, exhilarated, so smug?
Ah
Give me more 愛|<あ#|いを
give me more a i o
再多给我些 爱
Give me more love
Ah
右|<み#|ぎも左|<ひ#|だ#|りも 知|<しりもしないで言|<いわないで
mi gi mo hi da ri mo shi ri mo shi na i de i wa na i de
左右都分不清 一无所知就别妄言
Don't say that you don't even know left from right
Don't you think? Don't you think?
难道你不觉得？
ニヤリ影|<か#|げが笑|<わ#|らう
ni ya ri ka ge ga wa ra u
咧嘴一笑 暗影在笑
Your sneering shadow cackles
Hey!
世|<せ界|か#|いは大|<た#|い概|がい
se ka i wa ta i ga i
世界这东西 大抵
Generally speaking, the world is
Hey!
C,R,A,Z,Y
c r a z y
疯·狂·至·极
Hey!
繰|<くり返|<か#|えすように
ku ri ka e su yo u ni
仿佛循环往复
So as if doing it over and over
Ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
疾驰不停
ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
Hey!
わかってもいない
wa ka tte mo i na i
明明什么都不懂
I don't even understand it
Hey!
アレコレAuthorize
a re ko re authorize
却对这个那个 指手画脚
I authorize this and that
Hey!
Tell me something for the new 偉|<い大|だ#|いな期|<き待|た#|いの時|<じ代|だ#|いのバイ|<biブル|ble
tell me something for the new i da i na ki ta i no ji da i no bible
告诉我吧 为那崭新伟大期待时代的圣经
Tell me something for the news, the bible for an era of great expectation
CLAP BACK
狠狠回击
Losin' my mind shooting my side
迷失心智 击中我自身
Save it あなたのその瞬|<しゅ#|ん間|かん
save it a na ta no so no shun kan
握紧它 属于你的那个瞬间
Save it for your big moment
Maybe nothing wrong, nothing wrong
或许根本没错
La-dee-la-lee-la-la la-lee-la
Hey!
誰|<だ#|れもが大|<だ#|い体|たい C,R,A,Z,Y
da re mo ga da i ta i c r a z y
谁人都大抵 疯·狂·至·极
Generally speaking, everyone's C,R,A,Z,Y
Hey! Hey!
一|<い#|っ瞬|しゅ#|んの感|<か#|ん情|じょうに
i sshu n no ka n jo u ni
任由那一瞬间的感情
So let this fleeting emotion
Ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
疾驰不停
Hey!
心|<こ#|こ#|ろは95 狂|<きょう気|きのサムライ
ko ko ro wa ninety five kyo u ki no sa mu ra i
心跳至九五 狂气的武士
My heart is beating 95, like a mad samurai
Hey! Hey!
血|<ち走|ば#|しらせた目|<めで引|<ひくくらい Ready to die
chi ba shi ra se ta me de hi ku ku ra i ready to die
以血红的眼引人侧目 随时赴死
I'm so ready to die that it's like it's attracting my bloodshot gaze
ハ|<heロー|llo陽|<ひは昇|<の#|ぼり
ha ro o hi wa no bo ri
哈喽 太阳升起
Say hello as the sun rises
あなたの空|<そ#|ら 真|<まっ黒|<く#|ろな空|<そ#|ら
a na ta no so ra ma kku ro na so ra
你的天空 漆黑如墨的天空
On your sky, that pitch black sky
荒|<あ#|ら々|あ#|らしく引|<ひきちぎって
a ra a ra shi ku hi ki chi gi tte
狂暴地将它撕裂
I'll rip it apart with my bare hands
ホラその場|<ば所|しょで
ho ra so no ba sho de
看啊 就在那个地方
You see, in that place
聞|<きこえてくる鼓|<こ動|ど#|うの仕|<し掛|かけ
ki ko e te ku ru ko do u no shi ka ke
传来心跳律动的机关
There's the trick of an audible heartbeat
驚|<お#|ど#|ろくのはまだこれから
o do ro ku no wa ma da ko re ka ra
令人震惊的 还在后头
More surprises are yet to come
まだこれから
ma da ko re ka ra
才刚要开始
Yet to come
嗚|<あ呼|あもう待|<まち侘|<わびて
a a mo u ma chi wa bi te
早已等得迫不及待
Ah, I'm sick of waiting around
時|<と計|け#|いの針|<は#|り 零|<れ#|い時|<じの街|<ま#|ち
to ke i no ha ri re i ji no ma chi
时钟的指针 零时的街道
The clock hand ushers the midnight city
猛|<た#|け々|だ#|けしくいざ Rai|<ライse|ス your|<ユア vo|<ボi|イce|ス
ta ke da ke shi ku i za ra i su yu a bo i su
勇猛无畏 来吧 放声高喊
Come on, fiercely raise your voice
ホラすぐそこで
ho ra su gu so ko de
看啊 就在不远处
Hey, it's almost time
始|<は#|じまり出|<だす 孤|<こ高|こ#|うの宴|<う#|た#|げ
ha ji ma ri da su ko ko u no u ta ge
即将开启 孤高的盛宴
So let's begin this solitary feast
奏|<か#|なでるのは己|<お#|の#|れの調|<し#|らべ
ka na de ru no wa o no re no shi ra be
奏响的是自己的旋律
The song I play is my own tune:
唯|<ゆ#|い一|い#|つ無|<む二|にの己|<お#|の#|れの調|<し#|らべ
yu i i tsu mu ni no o no re no shi ra be
独一无二 属于自己的旋律
My one of a kind tune